doobop.com 2014-07-08

# Privacy Policy - DooBop

## Our Privacy Policy – Introduction

This Privacy Policy guides how we collect, store, and use the information that you provide to us. By providing your personal information to us, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and agree that we may collect, use, and disclose your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Terms and Conditions which govern your use of the website maintained and operated by DOOBOP (the "Site"). 

  By using the Site and by providing your personal information to us, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to agree to our Privacy Policy, then you should cease use of our Site and you should therefore immediately exit the Site. You should also immediately exit the Site if you are accessing the Site in a country or other territory where use of the Site is not permitted. 

  For more information about the terms of use for this site, please visit our Terms of Use page. 

  We will use your personal information only for the purposes set out below. 

  Although we are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust in all of our activities with you, this Privacy Policy does not govern our collection or use of personal data about you from sources other than the Site. 

  We may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We recommend that you regularly check this page to ensure that you have read the most recent version. 

  If you are under the age of 18, you must inform a parent or guardian about DOOBOP's Privacy Policy and Terms of Use and obtain his or her consent to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use before registering or placing and order with DOOBOP. 

  DOOBOP will ask you for information, including some personal information, if you use services available on the Site as further explained below. 

##   
Information we collect

The Site collects certain information when you interact with the Site. For example, the Site may collect “personal information", by which we mean data that can be used to identify an individual, as defined by applicable law. An example of this data is the information you provide from when you complete the registration form.  This information can include your name, email address, date of birth, telephone number and other identifying information. We may also collect include other personally-identifiable information such as your attitudes and opinions about our products, interests, household or lifestyle information, demographic data, satisfaction with our website and newsletters and your purchasing and browsing behavior. 

  The Site may also collect data that does not identify you specifically (non-personal information). In some instances, we may aggregate this non-personal information with personal information, such as combining your name with your geographic location or your browsing history. We will consider the combined information to be personal information as long as it is combined. 

  In addition, we may aggregate personal information that we collect with information we receive about you from outside sources. 

##   
Becoming a Registered User of DOOBOP.COM

In order to become a registered user of DOOOP.COM , you need to share some personal information, such as your name and e-mail address. You do not have to be a registered user to visit the Site. But you will have to register if you want to purchase products, to contribute any User Content (as defined in the Terms of Use), or more generally to make full use of our services. Once you register, you will have an account with DOOBOP and a password to access that account. 

  You should keep all your registration information current. You can do this by directly on the Site or you can also send us an email at the following address: [care@doobop.com](mailto:care@doobop.com)..   You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password. Please also let us know if there is any unauthorized use of your account or password. We recommend that you always log out from your account at the end of a session with us to prevent other people from accessing your account without your permission. 

##   
Purchasing Products on DOOBOP.COM

When you place an order on doobop.com, you have to supply a billing address, telephone number, shipping address, and credit card information. By making a purchase, you become a registered user of doobop.com. You can choose to store information needed to make a purchase, such as your credit card number, shipping and billing addresses in the My Profile page.

## Our Reviews or Question & Answer services 

If you are not already a registered user, you will become one when you use the Reviews or the Question & Answer service, and any personal information you submit will become part of your profile, as maintained by DOOBOP.

## Public Information 

If you choose to share information about yourself in an open format, such as through a site like Facebook or Twitter or in the User Content that you post on our Site, we will treat that information as public information.

## How DOOBOP Protects Your Information

We understand that our customers expect us to protect their personal information, and we take this responsibility seriously. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information that include industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") authentication to guarantee the confidentiality of online transactions made on our site. SSL authentication and encryption of the information that you send to us over the Internet help protect your online transaction information from third party interception. 

  However, no method of internet transmission or electronic storage is 100% secure or error-free, so we unfortunately cannot guarantee absolute security. 

  In addition, we cannot ensure the security of data during transmission to us or the security of your data on an iPhone (or various other mobile or fixed devices) or on your Twitter page. 

  Accordingly, despite our efforts, there is always a risk that communications may be unlawfully intercepted or disclosed. If you have reason to believe that your communications with us are no longer secure please immediately notify us by contacting us at the following email address: [care@doobop.com]. 

  As a result, you should be aware that you transmit all information to DOOBOP at your own risk. 

## How DOOBOP Uses Your Personal Information

We gather information about Site traffic, sales, wish list, and other commercial information which we may pass on to third parties but this information does not include any of your personal information. We strive to limit use of your personal information to those offers that we think you would appreciate receiving. 

  Finally, we may use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, together with non-personal data to monitor customer patterns so we can continually improve our site design to better meet our visitors' needs. If we change our policy on disclosure to others, we will inform you and give you the choice of opting out. 

  In the event that another company buys the assets or stock of DOOBOP, your personal information may then belong to another entity. 

## How to Avoid Receiving Newsletters and Other DOOBOP Materials

We may also use e-mail addresses and mailing addresses to send out newsletters and other announcements to you and our other customers with information about new products and special features. If you receive an e-mail and want to avoid further messages, go to the end of the e-mail for instructions on how to remove yourself from the mailing list. You can also edit your e-mail preferences at doobop.com's My Profile page. 

## Who Outside DOOBOP Views Your Personal Information?

DOOBOP uses various third party service providers to perform services on our behalf, and we may share your personal information with such service providers. The services provided by third parties include order fulfillment services, technical support, e-commerce services, credit card processing, investigations of potentially fraudulent activity, conduct of customer surveys, and other customer service functions. However, we do not authorize these third parties’ to use your personal information for purposes other than for which it has been provided, and we do not authorize these third parties to disclose that information to unauthorized parties or use that information for their direct marketing purposes. 

  Some personal information is stored on servers owned by other companies. Except as otherwise described below, only DOOBOP has the right to access this information.  

  Please be mindful of the fact that any personal information that you include in your profile or in any User Content you submit to the Site will be displayed without restriction on our Sites, and is subject to the provisions of our Terms of Use regarding User Content.  

## Personal information may be disclosed if required by law.

Personal information may be stored and processed in any country where DOOBOP stores data, and when you use the Site, you consent to transfer of your personal information to locations that may be outside the United States. 

  DOOBOP does not currently sell or license personal information to third parties for marketing purposes. If DOOBOP changes this policy, we will post a notice on the Site. However, we currently share aggregate information about our customers with advertisers and marketing partners. This information does not identify individual users and includes certain data about the Site, including number of visits, number of clicks or downloads and the number and types of purchasers of various products available on the Site. 

## Cookies

We use "cookies" to help us gather and store information about visitors to our Site.  This is a common practice among e-commerce websites. A cookie is a small data file that our server sends to your browser when you visit the Site. The use of cookies helps us to assist your use of certain aspects of the Site. You can delete cookies at any time or you can set your browser to reject or disable cookies. 

  We may use information from cookies, sometimes in combination with personal information that you have provided to us, to do the following things, which are provided by way of example (i.e., we may make other uses of such information): 

  \--compilation of statistics about our users in terms of numbers, traffic patterns and related site information; 

  \--recognition of repeat visitors; 

  \--monitoring of your use of the Site in order to provide you with information via email that is most relevant to your while also informing you of parts of the site that you have not visited; 

  \--traffic monitoring, which consists of identifying the IP address from which you access the Site, the type of browser and operating system used to access the site, the date and time of your access to the site, the pages you visit, and the Internet address of the website from which you accessed our Site; 

                                               \--anonymous tracking of interaction with online advertising, for example, to monitor the number of times that a banner ad is displayed and the number of times it is clicked. 

  We may collate the information that we collect through cookies with other personal information that you provide to us in order to customize or personalize your experience of the Site; for example, so that we can greet you on the Site by name. We may also use this collated information for transactional purposes, such as credit/debit card sales. 

  If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use most of the features of our website, including the ability to purchase items. 

DOOBOP also works with advertising partners (like Google, DoubleClick, Bing & Yahoo) that use cookies, pixel tags and other tracking technologies to serve advertisements on behalf of their retail clients, including DOOBOP, across the Internet, including to you after you have visited our Sites. These advertising partners engage in remarketing, online behavioral advertising and ad delivery and reporting. With respect to DOOBOP, these advertising partners may collect anonymous information about your browser as it makes visits to websites across the Internet (including our Sites) and your interaction with our advertising and e-mail communications. This anonymous information may also be used to tailor advertising for you and others elsewhere on the Internet. DOOBOP will have access to the information collected by these advertising partners and can then use it in combination with personally identifiable information provided by you to DOOBOP to enhance your experience on our Site. We will not share that personally identifiable information with these advertising partners. If you would like more information about this practice or would like to know your choices about not having your information used by these companies, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

## Children Under the Age of 13

The Site is not directed or intended for use by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect, and we do not wish to collect, personal information from children under the age of 13.  If you are under the age of 13, you can look at our Sites, but you cannot do any of the following things: make a purchase, become a registered user, provide User Content, or use other services that may be available on the Site.   
**  
 **

## Social Networks and Other Third Parties

We work with trusted third parties, including social network sites like Facebook, and with application developers who specialize in social commerce so we can connect to your social networks. Other social networks we use include Twitter, Instagram, and Tumblr. All of these companies operate websites. We provide access to our Site by third parties and business partners so we can generate interest in our products among members of your social networks and to allow you to share product interests with persons with whom you are connected on these networks. 

  However, this Privacy Policy governs only information that we collect through our Site, and not to websites, services or applications that do not link to this Privacy Policy or that are maintained and controlled by other companies or organizations, including third party websites. The collection and use of your personal information by and through third party websites, applications or other means will be governed by the privacy policies applicable to those third parties. 

  For example, information that you may provide to a third party site which is subsequently made available to us by that site is considered "public information" by us because the third party sites made it publicly available. If you do not want us to be able to access information about you from third party sites, you must instruct each of them not to share the information. It is up to you to make sure you understand the information they are sharing and the procedures for limiting the information that is shared by those other sites. 

## Further Information

If you require further information about our Privacy Policy, please go to the help section of the Site where frequently asked questions (FAQ's) are answered, and if you require more information after that please go to the Contact Us section of the Site and send an e-mail to the relevant DOOBOP department. If you wish to talk to a DOOBOP customer care representative please contact us on: +1 855 366 2671. You may also write to us at: 

    DooBop   
154 Grand Street  
New York, NY 10013
